你好吗
How we doin'?
今天是全年压力最大的日子
It's the most stressful day of the year
是对克莱尔来说
for Claire --
今天是结婚周年纪念日
our anniversary.
她总是到最后关头才去选礼物
She tends to leave her gift shopping till the last minute,
弄得自己压力很大
and the pressure can really get to her.
我很好啊
I'm great.
-你是不是忘了今天是... -我没忘
- Oh, did you forget it's our -- - No.
周年纪念日快乐
Happy Anniversary.
你平静得很离奇
You're strangely calm.
这是传说中疯到极点后的返疯归真之域吗
Is this the legendary realm beyond madness.
你的礼物我已经买好了
I already got your gift.
我选得特别成功
And I nailed it.
而且没有超过一百块钱的预算限制
I even stayed below the $100 limit.
你呢
You?
你会很满意的
Oh, you'll be quite pleased.
等我找到礼物后
...once I find something.
这次我等到最后一刻才去买礼物
This time I left my shopping till the last minute,
可能是为了给克莱尔一个竞争的希望
maybe just to give Claire a chance at our competition.
我太好胜了吗
Am I too competitive?
她确实常说
I mean, she does often say,
"菲尔 你每次都要先到终点[高潮]吗"
"Phil, do you always have to finish first?"
乔 我来抓你啦
Joe, I'm coming for you.
你们见到乔了吗
Hey, have you guys seen Joe?
大兄弟
Aw, man!
你这么轻易就找到我了
You found me so easy.
但好玩就好啦
But that was for fun.
躲猫猫
Hide and seek?
当我4岁小屁孩吗
What am I, 4?
我来是因为卢克有最新的丧尸电子游戏
I'm here because Luke has the new zombie video game
我妈绝不会让我玩
that my mom would never let me play.
还有什么
So...what else?
还有什么能玩呢
What else?
对了 你不是买了新的游戏吗
Hey, didn't you get a new video game?
糟了 糟了 糟了 糟了
Crap, crap, crap, crap, crap!
-你昨天看到她了吗 -没有 怎么了
- Did you see her yesterday? - No, why?
她发现自己睡过了一整天
That's what she says when she realizes
就会这样骂
she just slept through an entire day.
我老板周末外出了
So, my boss went away for the weekend,
我发现我把手机落在她家了
and I realized I left my phone at her house.
有一扇狗狗门可以进去
There's a doggy door,
但那样我就得先找只狗
but then I would have to find a dog,
想办法训练它进屋里去
somehow learn how to train it
再找到我的手机
to go inside, and then find it.
-我不知道上哪儿去找... -亲爱的
- And I don't know where to get a -- - Honey...
天啊 我这都没想到
Oh my God, duh.
乔 你不就有只狗吗
Joe, you have a dog.
走吧
Come on.
看到没 那时娱乐行业还是有格调的
Now see, this is when entertainment was classy.
老艺人身穿礼服
Max Feldman wore a tux,
观众抽着雪茄
the audience smoked cigars.
他的表演放到今天看 仍然跟七零年代时一样好笑
And his act is as fresh today as it was in the '70s.
怎么 你是爱斯基摩人吗
What are you, an Eskimo?
你懂50种雪的不同称呼
You got 50 words for "snow,"
但却不懂"牙刷"怎么叫
but apparently none for "toothbrush."
我不懂你们为什么喜欢这男的
I don't understand why you guys like that man.
他就是个欺负人的恶霸
He's a bully.
这就是为什么
See, this is why
我们今晚才不带你去看他的表演
we're not bringing you to his show tonight.
你听不懂笑话的哏
You don't get the jokes,
总是问个不停
you ask questions the whole time...
那会毁了观看感受
It ruins the experience.
我听得懂好笑的笑话
I understand funny jokes.
这不是好笑 是恶毒
This is not funny. This is mean.
他刚刚对那男的说
He just told that guy
他看起来像穿着晚礼服的牛肉干
that he looked like a beef jerky wearing a tuxedo.
那个男的是罗纳德·里根 他爱死这笑话了
And that guy was Ronald Reagan and he loved it!
我希望费尔德曼今晚也吐槽我
I hope Feldman zetzes me tonight.
-所以你才穿上这件丑爆的衣服吗 -不是
- Is that why you're wearing that shirt? - Huh? No.
我要出门去办些事
Anyways, I'm gonna go and run some errands.
如果豪尔赫在我回来之前就到了
If Jorge arrives before I'm back,
拜托你们不要用这些玩意烦他
please don't bore him with this stuff.
豪尔赫是个骚气美型的拉丁音乐人
Jorge was this steamy Latin musician
你妈跟他交往过
your mother used to date.
显然她觉得必须邀请他来家里
Apparently she feels she has to invite him here,
而不是边翻看高中年刊
instead of just thinking about him
配着第三杯威士忌
while she pages through a high-school yearbook
边想着他
on her third Scotch
像个正常人一样
like a normal person.
杰 别吃醋
Jay, don't be jealous.
那都是20年前的事了
It was 20 years ago,
再说我们只交往了6个月而已
and I only dated him for six months.
我们的感情远不如我跟你之间的深刻
And we never had what you and I have.
这话听了还挺开心
Well, that's nice to hear.
我只是沉迷他的肉体而已
It was only physical.
曼尼
Manny...
你今天要学点新知识
you're gonna learn something today.
我每天都尽量学习新知识
I try to learn something every day.
那让我保持青春活力
It keeps me young,
用芬兰语说就是"牛哦狸"
or nuori, as they say in Finnish.
假设你能不再说这种瞎话
Assuming you stop saying stuff like that,
终有一天你会娶到老婆
one day you will be married,
然后前任就会出现
and eventually the ex will show up
东闻西闻想抢你老婆
sniffing around,
挺起他小鲜肉的胸膛
puffing out his pretty-boy chest,
那时你就要拿出你的兽王气概
which is your cue to go alpha.
妈妈看到你对她老朋友不礼貌
Don't you think Mom will get annoyed
你觉得她不会生气吗
when she sees you being rude to an old friend?
完全不会
Not at all.
内心深处 她想看到我
Deep down, she wants to see me vanquish
完虐其他追求者
all who came before.
这是最基本的动物界原理
It's basic animal stuff.
我懂
Oh, I get it.
前几天晚上 我女友凯伦的前男友出现后
My girlfriend Karen was pretty frisky the other night
我跟他来了一场巧克力梳芙厘烘烤大对决
after her ex showed up, and I bested him
在我打败她后 她心情也很好
in a chocolate-souffle bake-off.
我不说你也能猜到
I don't need to tell you
她那晚"吃掉"的巧克力色甜点
my souffle wasn't the only sweet brown dish
不止我的梳芙厘
she devoured that night.
因为...
Because...?
我还做了黑糖曲奇
I also made molasses cookies.
所以我才学会了要问第二个问题
I've learned to ask the second question.
我都不记得为什么事打架了
I don't even remember what the fight was about.
那你的老师为什么想跟我们谈谈
Then why does your teacher want to have a chat with us?
可能她交不到朋友吧
Maybe she has trouble meeting people.
那是... 好大胆
Oh, that is a -- that's bold.
-太年轻了 是不是 -不会
- It's too young, isn't it? - No!
妈呀 这些玩意现在还能测谎了
Oh god, these things have lie detectors now.
先生 请给我看看你的袋子
Sir, please give me your bag.
估计是收银员
Oh...we-- well, the cashier probably
忘记取下防盗牌了
just forgot to take a security tag off of the --
这是从哪儿来的
Where did that come from?
疑似出现488情况
Possible 488.
不是啦 我怎么会偷胸罩
No. I wouldn't steal a bra!
我又不穿胸罩
I don't wear bras!
可能就穿过一次
Oh. Well, maybe once.
我们的朋友胡娇办过"五十岁好累[变装]派对"
Our friend Pepper had a "Turning 50 is a Drag" party.
他办过五次五十岁生日派对了
Yeah, he's had five of those.
-你懂的 -先生 请随我来
- So... - Sir, please come with me.
不 不不不
No... No, no, no, no, no.
米奇尔 打电话叫律师
Mitchell, call a lawyer!
我就是律师
I'm a lawyer.
可你输过的官司[丢掉的西装]
Yeah, but you've lost more suits
比遭遇龙卷风的西装大卖场还多
than a Men's Wearhouse in a tornado.
愚人节快乐
April Fool's!
他们以为你是商店扒手 傻了吧
They thought you were a shoplifter! Burn!
在学校和人打架 现在又搞偷窃恶作剧
A fight at school, and now a shoplifting prank?
如果你这是叛逆期
If you wanted to rebel,
为什么不能染一缕粉头发
why don't you just put a pink streak in your hair?
我说过了我不想染
I told you, I don't want one.
可你会看起来很可爱的
But you would look so cute.
好吧 无论你这是什么阶段
Okay, well, whatever this phase is,
-我可不喜欢 -这都怪我们
- I'm not a fan. - I blame us.
-我们太纵容她了 -同意
- We've been far too permissive. - Agreed.
你被禁足一个月 小姑娘
You are grounded for one month, Missy!
太阳马戏团的票已经买了
We got the Cirque du Soleil tickets.
-除了去看太阳马戏团 -和迪斯尼乐园之旅
- Except for Cirque du Soleil! - And the Disneyland trip.
和迪斯尼乐园之旅
And for Disneyland!
但今晚不准你去克里斯蒂娜的睡衣派对
But you are not going to Christina's slumber party tonight
-无论... -我们今晚订了仙人掌酒店了
- no matter how much -- - We have reservations at Cactus.
好吧 克里斯蒂娜的睡衣派对之后
Okay, Christina's slumber party
近期都不准出去玩
is the last one for a while.
没错 没错
Right. That's right.
香薰蜡烛
Scented candles.
愚人的选择
The simpleton's choice.
完美的礼物要有三个元素
The perfect gift has three elements --
不能是你会买给自己的东西
not something you'd buy for yourself,
能勾起人的情感回忆
takes you on an emotional journey,
并且勾得很有技巧
that journey is on a ship --
表演技巧
A showmanship.
想找到具备三元素的礼物很难
I mean, finding a gift that has all three is challenging,
但重点是 坏点子不是你的敌人
but here's the thing. Bad ideas aren't your enemy.
事实上 有时如果你根据坏点子
In fact, sometimes if you free-associate
展开自由联想 就能发现好点子
from the bad ideas, you discover great ones.
我们试试看
Let's try it.
先生 您到底想不想买盆栽
Sir, would you like a bonsai tree?
新奇钥匙链
Novelty key chain.
跳进脑海的第一个点子
First thing that popped into the noodle.
糟透了
It's terrible.
我们看看能解锁什么好主意
Let's see what that key unlocks.
新奇钥匙链
Novelty key chain.
新奇的锁
Novelty lock.
尼斯湖水怪
Loch Ness Monster.
越野摩托车
Monster bike.
车锁 挂锁
Bike lock. Padlock.
鼠标垫 新奇鼠标垫
Mouse pad. Novelty mouse pad!
新奇钥匙链
Novelty key chain!
什 么 鬼
What...just...happened?
就像我的灵感女神消失了一般
It was like my muse just disappeared.
她一去不回了
And she wasn't coming back.
香皂 她又不是你外婆 菲尔
Soap?! She's not your grandma, Phil!
如果我都不在乎它能拖地 拂尘
If I don't care that it mops, dusts,
有刮水板 有照明
squeegees, and lights up,
我为什么会在乎斯泰西·基齐[演员]说
would I care that Stacey Keach says
有了它别的清洁工具都不能入眼
it's the last cleaning tool you'll ever need?
一盒巧克力
Box of chocolates.
巧克拉伯爵[一种麦片]
Count Chocula.
夏卡·康[歌星] 骗子 曼岛
Chaka Khan, conman, Isle of Man.
《我爱露西》 刘玉玲
"I Love Lucy," Lucy Liu.
露露柠檬[服装品牌] 柠檬皮
Lululemon, lemon peel.
《基和皮尔》 钥匙链
"Key & Peele," Key chain!
新奇钥匙链
Novelty key chain?!
不
No!!
No!
-洗衣服很烦吧 -洗不完的衣服
- Laundry, right? - Oh, it never ends.
说得没错
I heard that.
-对了 结婚纪念日快乐 -谢谢
- Happy Anniversary, by the way. - Thank you.
你给菲尔买什么特别的礼物了吗
Did you get anything special for Phil?
这孩子演得太溜了
Kid's smooth like butter.
就像我教他的一样
Just like I coached him.
我给菲尔准备的礼物让我特别激动
I am very excited about the present I got for Phil.
到这来 走近点
Come on over here. Come on closer.
但你必须保证 你不会告诉任何人
But you have to promise that you are not gonna tell anybody.
快让我听听
Talk to papa.
我不想让其他任何人听到是什么
I don't want anybody else to hear what it is.
这是个特别棒的秘密
It's a really good secret.
礼物就是
And the present is...
你为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?!
我的耳朵还在发育阶段呢
My ears are still developing!
想得美 菲尔
Nice try, Phil.
真好笑
That's so funny!
亲爱的 你好吗
Oh. Hey, honey. How are you?
不好意思 我得接个电话
I'm so sorry. I have to take this.
老天
Oh, boy.
你好 罗伯特
Hello, Robert...
不怎么样 你呢
Not too much. How are you?
有很多方法可以在豪尔赫这样的男人面前
There are a lot of ways you can establish status
树立你的权威
over another man, like Jorge.
有力的握手
A firm handshake...
展示财富
displays of wealth...
展示力量
and feats of strength.
真有趣
Interesting.
我需要练习踢踏舞时
Moving that rug was the hardest thing
让你搬这块地毯就难于登天
in the world for you when I needed to practice tap dancing.
还有许多细微的招数
There are also more subtle moves,
我称之为微型攻击
what I call micro-aggressions.
叫错他的名字
Call him by the wrong name.
让他一见面就处于下风
Throws him off the moment he meets you.
你肯定是韦沃斯
You must be Huevos!
杰 幸会
Jay! Pleasure.
豪尔赫·德拉塞尔瓦
Jorge de la Selva.
用英语说就成《森林泰山》了
In English, it's George of the Jungle,
所以我一直只用西语发音
so I stick with Spanish.
是谁品味这么好
Hey, who's got the great taste?
是我
That would be me!
有品
Nice!
你好
Uh, hello...
你和歌洛莉亚...过去...
So, you and Gloria... you used to, uh...
是的
Yep.
他的英俊程度是超出了你的预期
Hey, so he was a little more handsome than you were expecting,
但打起精神来 伙计
but pull yourself together, man.
在莉莉这个年纪打架是很常见的
Now, fights are very common at Lily's age.
有许多家长问我
I mean, so many parents ask me,
"我家可爱的宝贝哪去了"
"What happened to my sweet little kid,"
我会说"这就是青春期"
and I say, "That's puberty."
青春期 莉莉还没到那个年纪吧
Puberty. Well, Lily's a little young for that, so...
不好意思
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
这是什么 内耳结构吗
What is this? The inner ear?
那是女性生殖系统
That is the female reproductive system.
小卡
Cam.
我弄掉了...
I dropped the, uh --
我想叫它卵道
I want to say egg chute,
但我知道它的学名应该会更拉丁语风一点
but I know it's probably something more Latin-y.
孩子进入青春期时
It can be a challenge
可能是个挑战
when a child enters into adolescence,
所以我想着
so I was thinking --
莉莉的生活中
does Lily have any aunts
有没有姑妈或者其他女性形象出现
or any other female figures in her life?
有 怎么了
Yes, why?
她也许会想跟一个女人聊聊
Well, she might want to talk to a woman
她在经历的事
about what she's going through.
我懂了
Okay. I see.
意思是作为同性恋恋人
So meaning, as a gay couple,
我们无法胜任
we're not up to the task
靠自己抚养女儿的任务
of raising a daughter on our own.
-不是 -好吧
- No... - Okay.
米奇尔 我卡住了
Mitchell, I'm stuck.
我只是说莉莉也许会难为情
I'm just saying that Lily may be self-conscious
跟男人 就算是她爸爸们
talking to men -- even her dads --
聊一些特定的女性身体问题
about certain female body issues.
她跟你说了为什么打架吗
Did she tell you what the fight was about?
当然说了
Yes. Obviously.
是啊 我们是个开明的家庭
Yes, we are a very open family.
我们不会不跟进的
It's not like we wouldn't just not follow up.
她跟你们说了什么
And what did she tell you?
就是...
Uh, that...
-一个 -男孩
- A... - Boy...?
-不是 -女孩
- No. - Girl.
一个女孩想扯莉莉的
A girl tried to snap Lily's --
-手指 -内衣
- Finger! - Bra.
-但莉莉没穿内衣 -正是
- But Lily doesn't have a bra. - Exactly.
现在她被嘲笑了
And now she's getting teased,
因为跟其他女孩不一样
because unlike the other girls,
她没有...
she doesn't have a --
直说吧 妈妈
Oh, just say it. A mom.
内衣
A bra.
好吧
Oh. Okay, so...
她把内衣塞进你包里
Oh, that wasn't a joke
并不是开玩笑
when she stuffed that bra in your bag.
她想要一件
She wants one.
她只是
She's just --
她只是不好意思要
she was too embarrassed to ask for it.
天啊
Oh, boy.
你觉得这事在睡衣派对上
You don't think this is gon-- gonna come up
不会被提起吧
at the slumber party, do you?
不会是克里斯蒂娜·S的睡衣派对吧
Not Christina S's slumber party?
-是啊 -天啊
- Yes. - Oh, God.
她的毒舌把我们的午餐大妈送回了疗养中心
She single handedly sent our lunch lady back to rehab.
我会强烈推荐给莉莉带...
I would strongly consider bringing Lily --
谢谢 我们知道了
Thank you, we got it.
你显然打算说
Obviously you were gonna say
我们该带...莉莉回家
we should bring Lily... home?
其实我是想说
Actually, I was going to say
给莉莉买件少女内衣
bring Lily a training...bra.
-少女内衣 -一套火车[少女]] 内衣
- Training bra! - A train set! Bra.
瞧 我们都同时说了少女内衣
See? We all said training bra at the same time.
这咖啡泡太棒了
Oh, wow. This crema is incredible.
秘诀是危地马拉的阿莫尔咖啡豆
The secret is Amore beans from Guatemala.
低酸 阴地生长
Low-acid, shade-grown,
每颗咖啡豆被一群山区修女给按摩过
individually massaged by an order of hill nuns.
我很熟悉阿莫尔咖啡豆
Oh, I'm very familiar with the Amore bean.
我能很理解你为什么没法
I get why you have trouble
打败这个人
vanquishing this guy.
-他太完美了 -豪尔赫
- He's perfect. - So, Jorge, um,
你是歌洛莉亚在哈维尔之前的男友
you were Gloria's boyfriend right before Javier?
是的 还有一小段时间重叠了
Yeah, and a little during, you know?
她在我俩之间徘徊不定
She kinda bounced around between the two of us.
她到底在哪儿呢
Um, where is she anyway?
我一小时后就要去道奇队比赛了
I got to be at a Dodger game in an hour.
你喜欢运动啊
Oh, you like sports?
太棒了
That's fantastic!
我试着让他喜欢棒球
I tried to get this one into baseball.
没成功
No go.
实际上我讨厌棒球
Actually, I hate baseball.
我是去唱国歌的
I'm here to sing the national anthem.
我是歌剧演唱家
I'm an opera singer.
我刚在斯卡拉大剧院唱了两个月
I just finished two months at La Scala.
托斯卡尼尼建造的剧院吗
The house that Toscanini built?!
那里被重建过几次啦
Yeah, well, it's been rebuilt a few times.
一群歌剧演唱家走来走去的
You know, a bunch of opera singers prancing around.
给地基带来的负担也不小
It, uh, takes its toll on the foundation.
-好吧 -嘿
- Yeah. - Hey.
我是来拿仓库里妈妈的音箱喇叭的
I'm here to pick up Mom's old boombox from storage?
她需要...
She needs it for...
你戴着这副眼镜能看见几个曼尼
How many Mannys do you see through these things?
那是歌洛莉亚的前男友
That's Gloria's ex-boyfriend.
等等 多久前的
Wait, how far ex?
大概20年前
Roughly 20 years.
天啊
Oh, my God.
这有可能吗 歌洛莉亚怎么说
Is -- Is it possible? What does Gloria say?
她还没看见他
She hasn't even seen him yet.
奇怪的是
The odd bit is,
这俩一模一样的人还没看出彼此容貌相似
these two clones don't see the resemblance.
也许她也看不出 我也不会逼她这么想的
Maybe she won't either? I'm not gonna force it on her.
这事情可不容易说
I mean, it's no easy thing to say
"你是不是有可能蠢到
"Is there a chance you're so dumb
不知道你孩子的爸爸是谁"
you don't even know who the father of your baby is?"
我们可以进行基因检测
We could do a DNA test.
我可以在学校实验室里做
I could do one at the lab at school.
这样你就有确定的答案了
And then you would have a definitive answer.
如果是阴性的
If it comes back negative,
你就没必要告诉歌洛莉亚了
mm, you don't even really have to tell Gloria.
你需要什么 唾液吗
Well, what do you need, saliva?
我们带他俩去吃自助餐
We take these two down to the Sizzler,
你从沙拉吧的窗上搜集他俩滴下来的口水
and you squeegee what you need off the salad-bar window?
现在都用头发了
They use hairs now!
"但我们昨天绞死了威奇托·威利"警长说
"But we hanged Wichita Willy yesterday," said the sheriff.
"会是他回来报仇吗"
"Could he be back for revenge?"
这时候他们抬起了头
That's when they looked up
看见了威奇托·威利
and there was Wichita Willy,
绞索还在他的脖子上晃来晃去
the noose still dangling from his neck.
亲爱的 你们干什么呢
Hey, sweetie. What you guys doing?
你听说过被绞死两次的威利吗
Have you heard of Twice Hung Willy?
嗯 我了解他的电影 但是...
Um, yes, I'm familiar with his films, but --
你们来干什么呢
What are you doing here?
我们忘记给你打包了一样东西
There's something we forgot to pack for you.
我能和你聊聊吗
Can -- can I talk to you for a second?
不行 这是女生派对
No. It's girls only.
我知道 但你会喜欢的
Yeah, no, but you're gonna love it.
是什么
What is it?
不是给你的 克里斯蒂娜
Oh, it's not for you, Christina.
莉莉
Lily...?
你爸爸怎么拿着个输卵管
Why does your dad have a fallopian tube?
原来是这个名字
That's what it is.
你们有什么毛病啊
What's wrong with you?!
冷静点 好吗
Calm down, okay?
你大爸在玩弄
Your father was fiddling
你老师的生殖器官
with your teacher's reproductive organ.
天啊 沃尔夫老师
Oh, my God! Ms. Wolfe?!
不 是她桌子上的模型
No, ju-- the model on her desk.
然后他把手指伸进去
And then he put his finger into it,
然后他出不...
and then he couldn't --
-我出不来了 -好吧 我来
- Well, now mine's stuck! - Okay, let me...
-好紧啊 -你把手指穿过去
- Okay, this is tight. - Push your finger through.
不
Oh, no.
真实生活中也是这样吗 我觉得不是
Are they like this in real life? I don't think so.
太恶心了
This is gross!
不 不恶心好吗
No. It's not gross, okay?
你身体的任何部分对我们来说都不会恶心
Nothing about your body is gross to us.
是的 你的生理周期不会 你的...
Yes. Not your cycles, not your fluids --
天啊 别再说了
Oh my God, just stop talking forever,
快走吧
Just go!
真是太糟糕了
Oh, well, that was a disaster.
或许是时候承认
You know, maybe it's just time we start to admit
异性恋伴侣
that straight couples have strengths
拥有我们没有的强项
that we don't, you know?
或许妈妈们比咱们更了解女儿
And maybe moms know more about girls than we do.
是时候转交女孩事宜了吗
Is it time to start farming some of this girl stuff out?
是啊 但交给谁呢
Yeah, but to who?
克莱尔和别人说的太多
Claire's an over-sharer.
歌洛莉亚 她的身体是人类的吗
Gloria -- is her body even human?
海莉比莉莉知道的还少
Haley knows less than Lily.
-那我们找谁 艾丽克斯吗 -我也认为
- So who do we go to? Alex? - I guess.
或许会很无聊 但至少正确的
I mean, it'll be dull, but it'll be right.
咱们再给米洛打个恶作剧电话吧
Let's prank call Milo again.
你喜欢他
You totally like him.
我才没有 我只是想折磨他
I do not! I just want to torture him.
好吧 我们听到这些
Okay -- so, see, are we supposed to hear something like that
-应该什么都不说吗 -是的
- and say nothing? - Yes, we are.
-快走 -各位
- Come on. - Okay, hi.
如果你们想要吸引男生的注意力
If you want to get a boy's attention,
恶作剧电话可能不是个好主意
you know, a prank call is probably not the move.
爸
Dad!
小卡 我们不应该插手
Cam, this is not our place.
但他没说错
But, he's not wrong.
我只是想让他抓狂
I just like to make him mad!
好吧 我们只是以为你喜欢他
Yeah, well, we just thought you liked him
你想知道
and you wanted to know
吸引他的好方法
the best way to get his attention,
但看来不是这样
but apparently not.
那晚安啦
So good night.
等下
Wait!
-好吧 谁是米洛最好的朋友 -巴雷特
- Okay. Okay, so, who's Milo's best friend? - Barrett.
好那你给米洛发短信 "你太好玩了
Okay, you're gonna text Milo, "You're hilarious!
笑哭表情加眨眼表情"
Crying-laughing face, and winky face emoji."
然后过一会儿
Then wait a beat.
你再发一条
Then you're gonna text back,
"哎呀抱歉 刚才是要发给巴雷特的
"Oops, sorry. That was for Barrett.
嘴巴一条线的没表情脸"
Neutral-face emoji with straight-line mouth."
天啊 太高招了
Oh my God. Genius.
我从没见过她笑
Wow, I've never seen her smile.
亲们
Dudes!
米洛回我短信了
Milo just texted me back.
好 他说了什么
Okay, what'd he say?
"你真讨厌
"You're a jerk.
吐舌头的眨眼表情"
Winky eye face with the tongue hanging out."
你有戏了
Oh, you're in. You're in.
别回复他知道吗
Do not text him back, okay?
但当你周一早上见他时
But when you see him on Monday,
走过他 然后给他来句
walk right past him and throw him a quick...
"嗨"
"Hey."
嗨 没错
Hey. Yes!
好了 你们继续吧
All right, you girls got it from here.
我们有晚餐订了餐厅
We have a dinner reservation.
我看到你们装到包里的东西了
Hey, I saw what you put in the bag.
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气亲爱的 我们爱你
You're welcome, sweetie. And we love you.
我喜欢男孩的时候你们还会这么酷吗
Are you gonna be this cool when I like a boy?
不不不 不可能
Oh, no. No. No. Not a chance.
-太好了 你回来了 -等一下
- Good, you're home. - One second.
宝贝 你穿这件新衬衫真是太漂亮了
Papi, you look great in that new shirt!
-太帅了 -歌洛莉亚
- So handsome! - Gloria!
我以为你是曼尼
I thought you were Manny.
很好 你现在看出来了
Good. You're caught up now.
我知道我有点胖了
I know I put on a few,
但作为歌剧演员太瘦的话
but they don't take you seriously as an opera singer
别人就不会把你当一回事儿
when you're too skinny.
你们知道瘦弱的女士演唱时会怎么样吗
Do you know what happens when the thin lady sings?
大家会以为之后还有
The show just keeps going.
见到你真是太好了
It's so wonderful to see you.
我要开瓶酒
I -- I'm gonna go and open a bottle of wine.
你觉得豪尔赫可能...
Do you think that Jorge could be...?
豪尔赫提到过
Jorge mentioned you bounced around
你他和哈维尔之间徘徊不定
between him and Javier.
你徘徊到什么样的地步
How much bouncing did you do?
严格来说 是可能的
Technically, it's possible.
我的老天
Oh, my God.
-曼尼对此会作何反应 -肯定不会好
- How is Manny going to handle this? - Not great.
你知道他不善于面对意外
You know he doesn't respond well to surprises.
记得他发现那些土豆泥
Remember how upset he got
实际上是花椰菜泥时
when he found out those mashed potatoes
他有多沮丧吗
were really just whipped cauliflower?
我们要怎么办
What are we going to do?
外公 我
Okay, Grandpa, I got --
歌洛莉亚你在这
Oh, Gloria, you're here.
除了那惭愧的表情之外你还带了什么
What do you bring with you, besides that guilty look?
为了得到确切的结果
Okay, in order to get a definitive answer,
我请艾丽克斯做了亲子鉴定
I had Alex perform a DNA test.
你让他俩都吐了唾沫了吗
You got them both to spit?
他们现在用头发测了
They use hair now. Eugh.
豪尔赫 乳液在水池上
Hey, lotion's on the sink, Jorge.
原来我不是唯一一个
Hey, turns out I'm not the only one
皮肤容易干的人
who suffers from dry naval.
艾丽克斯 为什么你拿着
Uh, Alex, why do you have a medical form
有我名字的医疗报告
with my name on it?
我认为不该由我来解释
I don't think I should be the one to explain this.
曼尼 你知道
Manny...as you know,
你妈妈和豪尔赫在一起过
your mother and Jorge had a relationship.
你和他很像
You're a lot alike,
所以我们好奇是不是
and it made us curious as to whether...
你是说...
Uh, are -- are you saying --
这是亲子鉴定
This is a DNA test.
你妈也是直到今天才发现
Your mom didn't even find out until today.
所以 我
So -- I--
我根本不知道该作何反应
I -- I don't even know how to react.
所以我的整个童年就是个谎言
So my whole childhood was a lie?
我以为哈维尔是我爸
I thought Javier was my dad.
现在他不过是个给我洗澡的陌生人
Now he's just some stranger who gave me baths?
听着 孩子
Listen, buddy.
谁将你带到这个世上并不重要
It's not who brings you into the world.
你在这个世上做了什么才重要
It's what you do when you're there.
你不是哈维尔
You're not Javier.
你也不是这个家伙 你就是你
You're not this guy. You're you.
你很棒
And what you are is amazing.
你听我说
And for the record,
从你十岁起我就成为你的爸爸
I've been your dad since you were 10,
我至死都是你的爸爸
and I'm gonna be your dad until I'm gone.
我爱你 永远都爱你
I love you, and I always will.
杰 我也爱你
I love you too, Jay.
愚人节快乐
Ha! April Fool's!
现在是谁不懂笑话啊
Now who doesn't understand a joke?!
什么
What?
我从没跟豪尔赫在一起过
I never dated Jorge!
他是超市里的屠夫啦
He's the butcher at the grocery store!
我只是觉得他长得跟曼尼很像
I just thought that he looked like Manny!
你为什么要这么做啊
Why would you do that?
因为你们说我不懂幽默
Because you said that I didn't understand funny.
我之前没想到你会整到这么狠
I didn't know you were going to take the prank this far.
你都害外公哭了
You made Grandpa cry.
对啊
I know!
看他刚那样子
He was like,
"我爱你 永远都爱你"
"I love you and I always will."
好了 我要走了
Okay, look, I'm out.
我曾养与屠宰过小牛
Uh, I used to raise veal,
但你这个是我这辈子
and this has to be the cruelest thing
参与过最残忍的事情了
I've ever been a part of.
快到了 就快到了
Okay, almost there... almost there...
等等 一秒
Hang on. One second.
克莱尔的礼物包含了眼罩
Claire's gift involved a blindfold
与第二地点
and a second location --
这是最高境界的表演技巧
showmanship of the highest order.
而我当时已经没时间了
To make things worse, the clock ran out on me.
我的礼物...
My gift...
凑数选了个...
I settled...
我都不好意思说出来
I can't even say it out loud.
准备...
And...
请看
Ta-da!
天啊
Oh, my God.
我们以前住的公寓
Our old apartment.
怎么样
I know.
我几周前在短租网站上随便看看
I was noodling around on Airbnb a couple of weeks ago
而这里正好在招租
and it was just right there listed.
真是不敢相信
Unbelievable.
一晚只要85块
It's $85 for the night,
我们以前最爱的炸鱼柳条6块
$6 for our old favorite Arizona fish sticks,
正在烤 你应该能闻到
which you will smell warming right now...
租电影《忘情巴黎》花了3块
...$3 for the "Forget Paris" rental.
你还找到了我们以前喜欢的瓶装红酒
Aw, you even found cans of the wine we used to like.
你真的选得很成功
You completely nailed it.
我知道 太成功了
I know. I really did!
我成功了 我成功了
I did! I did!
这也是我第一次成功
And it was the first time ever.
而且...
And...
我好希望这感觉能一直不散
I really want this feeling to last.
如果我要求你
Would it be weird if I asked you
明天再给我礼物 会不会很奇怪
not to give me your gift until tomorrow?
-满足你 -太棒了
- You got it. - Yes!
其实呢 我可能
In fact, I might, uh --
我可能会偷偷跑去把这个礼物给换掉
I might sneak off and trade this in
换成个很烂的东西
for something really terrible
让你更显大获全胜
just to seal your victory.
好了
All right.
现在让派对正式开始吧
Now let's get this party started.
不会吧
No. Mm.
我以前为你做的精选集吗
The old mixtape I made you?
没错 "菲尔之调合集"
Oh, yeah. "Songs in the key of Phil."
糟糕
Oh, no! Oh. Oh.
糟糕 等等
Aw, no. Wait, hang on.
-卷不回去了 -没事啦
- It's not going back in. - You know what?
有时候不听音乐也挺好的
Sometimes it's nice to not have music.
我才不要整晚听那个
Well, I'm not listening to that all night.
不知道当年的"对讲机系统"还好用不
I wonder if the old intercom system still works.
想起来了
Oh, yeah!
没错
Yeah.
狠狠地说他们
Give it to 'em.
挥洒我的情绪
Tell 'em how I feel.
天啊
Oh, my God!
没事的 没事 不用紧张
It's okay! Okay. No need to be alarmed.
鱼柳条别焦了啊
Oh, no, not the fish sticks!
菲尔 打开窗烟雾警报就会停了
Oh, oh, Phil? Open the window, and it'll stop the alarm!
-天啊 救命 -没事的
- Oh, God! Whoa! Oh, God! - Oh, it's okay!
-菲尔 菲尔 -我来救你
- Phil! Phil! - Oh! I got you!
-好 -我来救你
- Okay. - I got you!
天啊 天啊 天啊
Oh, God. oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
天啊 天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
红酒可燃吗
Wine is flammable?!
不可 但这种可以
No! But that is!
救命啊
Oh, God.
我了个浣熊
Raccoons!
求你了 要骂脏话就用大人用的词
Oh, for God's sake, Phil, just swear like an adult.
不是
No!
我内心的某个部分早料到我有天会这么死
Part of me always knew this is how I was gonna go out.
被浣熊围绕 死在红酒火灾中吗
In a wine fire surrounded by raccoons?
等等
Wait.
这是什么
What is that?
我的天啊
Oh, my goodness.
太赞了
Oh, yes.
这又是什么
What -- what is this?
太厉害了
Oh, yes!
-还不快滚 -你也给老子闭嘴
- Yeah! Get out! - You shut your mouth!
爽啊
Oh, yeah!
既然我们的邻居听不懂暗示
And since the neighbors can't take a hint.
这真是太屌了
That was amazing.
亲爱的老婆
My dear,
送给你最好的礼物
nothing but the best for you...
来纪念我们的结婚纪念日
...on our anniversary.
来
Now...
刚才说到哪了
...where were we?
能赏脸跳这支舞吗
May I have this dance?
可以
Yes.
我真是世界上最幸运的女孩
I am the luckiest girl in the world.
你结婚纪念日要送我拖...
Did you get me a mop for our --
给点力啊
Come on.
亲爱的 怎么了
Honey, what happened?
我弄撒了一点牛奶
I spilled some milk.
结果这拖把什么都能 就是不能拖地
Apparently the only thing this mop can't do is mop.
为此难过也没用
Well, there's no use crying over it.
直接打给他们投诉吧
Just call them and complain.
你说得对
Oh, you're right.
我是您的紧急拖把专员
This is your emergency moperator.
有何能为您效劳呢
How can I help?
我拖把的拖地功能坏了
The mop function on my mop isn't working.
我深感抱歉
I'm sorry to hear that,
我这就远端帮您重启拖把
I'm gonna go ahead and do you a remote reset.
您可能会发现拖把温度变得极高
You may notice your mop gets extremly hot.
我应该...
Should I...?
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
拖把专员 这个玩笑好
Good one moperator.
真希望你能看到他刚才的表情
You should've seen his face.
我看到了 你们真是一对有爱的夫妇
I did. You are an adorable couple.
-扔了它 -我这就...
- I rid of it. - I'm...